<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="51">
    <author>Wopster</author>
    <version>1.0.0.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>ProSeed</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed adds a bundle of functionality to enhance sowing machines in the game.
With ProSeed you're able to create tramlines (with optional pre-emergence marking), halfside shutoff for creating the perfect tramlines, fertilizer shutoff and active feedback with sounds.

For more information and how to use it read <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">the manual on my GitHub</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed erweitert Sähmaschinen mit neuen Funktionen um sie zu weiter zu verbessern.
Mit ProSeed kannst du Fahrgassen erstellen (optional mit Vorauflaufmarkierung), Sähmaschinen halbseitig abschalten um perfekte Fahrgassen erstellen zu können, die Unterfußdüngung kann optional deaktiviert werden und es gibt aktives feedback mit Sounds.

Für weitere Informationen, lese dir die <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">manual aus dem Github durch</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </de>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed ajoute un ensemble de fonctionnalités pour améliorer les semoirs dans le jeu.
Avec ProSeed, vous pouvez créer des lignes de passage (avec marquage de pré-levée en option), une fermeture à mi-chemin pour créer des lignes de passage parfaites, une coupure des fertilisants et un retour d'information actif avec des sons.

Pour plus d'informations, veuillez lire le manuel sur mon <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">Github</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </fr>
        <nl>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed voegt een bundel aan functies toe om zaaimachines in het spel te verbeteren.
Met ProSeed heb je de mogelijkheid om rijpaden te maken (met optionele voor-opkomst markering), halfzijdige uitschakeling om perfecte rijpaden te creëren, bemesting van kunstmest uit te schakelen en actieve feedback met geluid.

Voor meer informatie, lees de handleiding op mijn <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">GitHub</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </nl>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[La mod ProSeed aggiunge un pacchetto di funzionalità per migliorare le seminatrici nel gioco.
Con ProSeed è possibile creare delle carreggiate (opzionalmente per trattamenti di pre-emergenza), spegnere elementi di semina, disattivare il fertilizzante e avere un feedback sonoro.

For more information and how to use it read <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">the manual on my GitHub</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </it>
        <ru>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed добавляет набор функций для улучшения сеялок в игре.
С помощью ProSeed вы можете создавать технологические колеи (с опциональной маркировкой до появления всходов), отключение половины сеялки для создания идеальных технологических колей, отключение подачи удобрения и активную обратную связь со звуками.

For more information and how to use it read <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">the manual on my GitHub</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </ru>
        <cz>
            <![CDATA[ProSeed přidává mnoho funkcí pro vylepšení secích strojů ve hře.
S ProSeed můžete vytvořit kolejové řádky (s volitelným nastavením), vypnout polovinu secího stroje pro vytvoření dokonalého kolejového řádku, vypnout přihnojování hnojivem a aktivovat zpětnou vazbu se zvuky.

For more information and how to use it read <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">the manual on my GitHub</a>.

Changelog:
- Hotfix for tramline activation on wrong track number for even amount of lanes.
]]>
        </cz>
        <hu>
            <![CDATA[A ProSeed kiegészítő funkciókat ad hozzá a játékban található vetőgépekhez.
A ProSeed használatával a vetőgép képes lesz művelőnyomok létrehozására (opcionálisan kikelés előtt is), féloldali sor elzárásra a tökéletes művelőnyom eléréséhez, műtrágya adagolás kikapcsolására, valamint hanggal történő állapotvisszajezésre.

További információért, és a kezelési útmutató elolvasásához látogasd meg a <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/proSeed/blob/master/README.md">README oldalt a GitHub-on</a>. (csak angolul elérhető)
]]>
        </hu>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/loader.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="PS_SET_LANES_TILL_TRAMLINE" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="PS_SET_HALF_SIDE_SHUTOFF" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="PS_TOGGLE_MOUSE_CURSOR" axisType="HALF"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="PS_SET_LANES_TILL_TRAMLINE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_r"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_11"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="PS_SET_HALF_SIDE_SHUTOFF">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_t"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_3"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="PS_TOGGLE_MOUSE_CURSOR">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_MIDDLE"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_6 BUTTON_19"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
</modDesc>
